Коісні Іто

Singapore

koichi.ito@u.nus.edu
 https://github.com/koito19960406 https://koichiito.com/

Research Interests

A PhD student at the National University of Singapore and consultant at the World Bank Group, interested in researching human mobility and equity with emerging spatial data sources, such as street-view imagery, and machine/deep learning techniques.

Education

The National University of Singapore

Aug 2022 - Present

PhD in Urban Analytics

Singapore

- Ongoing projects supervised by Dr. Filip Biljecki:
 - 1. Python package for street view imagery analysis.
 - 2. EEG-based analysis of cyclists' visual perception.

The National University of Singapore

Aug 2019 - May 2021

Master of Urban Planning

Singapore

• 4.53/5.00 cumulative GPA (Highest Distinction)

Soka University of America

Aug 2015 - May 2019

Bachelor of Arts, Liberal Arts with Concentration in Environmental Studies

Aliso Viejo, CA

• 3.95 /4.00 cumulative GPA (summa cum laude)

Council on International Educational Exchange

Aug 2017 - Dec 2017

Study Abroad Program

Dakar, Senegal

Honors

• Singapore International Graduate Award (SINGA) Scholarship

Aug 2022 - Present

• Japan Student Services Organization Scholarship (US\$40,000)

Aug 2020 - May 2021

May 2019

• Soka University of America Makiguchi Scholarship (US\$10,000) • Soka University of America Dean's List (GPA is 3.7 or higher)

Dec 2015 - May 2019

• Soka University of America Merit Scholarship (US\$20,000)

Aug 2015 - May 2019

Publications

- Ito, K., Bansal, P., & Biljecki, F. (2024). Examining the causal impacts of the built environment on active transportation using time-series street view imagery. Manuscript under review for publication in Transportation Research Part A: Policy and Practice.
- Ito, K., Quintana, M., Han, X., Zimmermann, R., & Biljecki, F. (2024). Sidewalk the Talk: Translating street view imagery to correct perspectives to enhance bikeability and walkability studies. Manuscript under review for publication in Transportation Research Part C: Emerging Technologies.
- Ito, K., Kang, Y., Zhang, Y., Zhang F., & Biljecki, F. (2024). Understanding Urban Perception with Visual Data: A Systematic Review. Manuscript under review for publication in Cities.
- Wang, Z., Ito, K., & Biljecki, F. (2023). Assessing the equity and evolution of urban visual perceptual quality with time series street view imagery. Cities, 145, 104704. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cities.2023.104704
- Ito, K., & Biljecki, F. (2021). Assessing bikeability with street view imagery and computer vision. Transportation Research Part C: Emerging Technologies, 132, 103371. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.trc.2021.103371
- Biljecki, F., & Ito, K. (2021). Street view imagery in urban analytics and GIS: A review. Landscape and Urban Planning, 215, 104217. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.landurbplan.2021.104217

Academic Journal Peer Review

| • Landscape and Urban Planning | Reviewed 2 times 2022, 2023 |
|---|--|
| • International Journal of Geographical Information Science | Reviewed 1 time 2023 |
| • Computational Urban Science | Reviewed 1 time 2023 |
| • Journal of Geographical Systems | Reviewed 1 time 2022 |
| • International Journal of Applied Earth Observation and Geoinformation | Reviewed 1 time 2022 |
| • Environment and Planning B: Urban Analytics and City Science | Reviewed 2 times 2021 , 2022 |

Talks and Poster Presentations

Gave a guest lecture talk at a GIS course at the National University of Singapore. Singapore

• "Sidewalk the Talk: Translating street view imagery to correct perspectives to enhance bikeability and walkability studies" Oct 2023 Singapore

Presented a poster at the Urban Solutions and Sustainability R&D Congress.

• "Evaluating active mobility and urban perception with visual data"

• "Street View Imagery: Have we answered all the questions with it? What's left to do?" Sep 2023

Organized a session at Spatial Data Science Symposium 2023. • "Application of GIS in research and international institution."

Oct 2021 Presented my research at Soka University of America, Advanced GIS Course. Online

Work Experience

The World Bank Group — Poverty and Equity Global Practice

Apr 2021 - Present

Consultant

Remote

Online

Oct 2023

- Developed and maintained interactive data dashboards using Shiny and Golem frameworks to facilitate spatial data visualization and analysis.
- Implemented spatial lag models in R to analyze factors correlated with poverty and stunting.
- Led the collection, cleaning, and mapping of various data sets including nighttime light, natural disaster metrics, household data, and accessibility indicators using R.
- Conducted a capacity-building program for the Tanzania's National Bureau of Statistics, imparting skills and knowledge on spatial analysis using R.

Johnson Controls Nov 2020 - May 2021

Data Analytics Intern

Singapore

- Constructed a data pipeline of PM2.5 data, weather data, and traffic data in Singapore on Azure Synapse for a real-time Power BI dashboard.
- Built a time-series model to predict PM 2.5 levels anywhere in Singapore in Python.

The World Bank Group — Tokyo Development Learning Center

Apr 2020 – Jan 2021

Urban Development Research Intern

Remote

- Compiled comprehensive data set of over 4,000 Tokyo-based startups' information, such as addresses, investors, and accelerators, using Python.
- Visualized financial performance of light rail transport system in Toyama prefecture between 2002 and 2019.

ENDA LEAD Afrique Francophone

Aug 2017 - Dec 2017

Research Intern

Dakar, Senegal

Authored a report on accessibility to potable water in 500 villages in the Saint-Louis region in Senegal.

Teaching Experience

AR5805 Advanced Architecture Studio

Aug 2023 - Dec 2023

Teaching Assistant

The National University of Singapore, Department of Architecture

 Assisted the lead professor with logistical and administrative tasks, including the preparation of course documents and aiding in the smooth operation of lectures.

Supervising

• Zeyu Wang, Master of Urban Planning

Aug 2022 - May 2023

Technical Skills

Languages: Japanese (native), English (fluent), French (limited working proficiency)

Computer Skills: Python, R, SQL, Spark, ArcGIS, QGIS, Google Earth Engine, Azure, AWS, Power BI

References

• Filip Biljecki

Presidential Young
(Assistant) Professor
College of Design and
Engineering, The National
University of Singapore

• Prateek Bansal

Presidential Young
(Assistant) Professor
College of Design and
Engineering, The National
University of Singapore

• Victor Mulas

Director World Bank Group, Tokyo Development Learning Center • Takaaki Masaki Senior Economist The World Bank, Poverty & Equity Global Practice